Mirosha Suresmaran

DATA ANALYST

- Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Mirosha-Suresmaran/9baef5a2a10da584

Dedicated and detailed oriented professional with over 4 years of workforce, management and call centre operations experience SKILLS SUMMARY. Experienced strategic and tactical planner Past phase reporting Strong technical skills Excel, forecasting, scheduling, and effective communication skills Analysis of KPI's to establish goals and metrics Scorecard and metric design.

Work Experience

DATA ANALYST

July 2018 to April 2019

SALARYRM3500)

- Managed a high-volume workload within a deadline-driven environment. Resolved an average of 200 inquiries in any given week and consistently met performance benchmarks in all areas (speed, accuracy, volume).
- Point person for all CMS IDs and extensions assigning to all new hires.
- Working close with the senior leadership to influence planning and support to drive the results according to the region goals, trends, and historical performances.
- Collaborating with the floor managers and resource managers to run the daily transactions smooth and results oriented with balancing both internal and external client experiences Adherence improvement measures through negotiating skills.
- Daily Service level forecasting on intraday basis and ensuring necessary scheduling adjustments to meet the staffing needs per FTE head COLI. Helped company attain the highest customer service ratings (as determined by external auditors) -- earned 100% marks in all categories including communication skills, listening skills, problem resolution and politeness.
- Officially commended for initiative, enthusiasm, tenacity, persuasiveness, intense customer focus and dependability in performance evaluations.
- Completed voluntary customer service training to learn ways to enhance customer satisfaction and improve productivity.
- Recognized as "#1 Customer Service Rep" (out of 20 reps in division) in Fall 2015. Ranking was based on accuracy, customer service, duration of calls and availability.
- Accurately collating of all core and non-core activities on a real-time basis to ensure up to date intraday forecasts and accuracy in shrinkage calculations which aid local MIS
- Variance reporting to customers, to enable them to make timely decisions about planned off line activities and outages
- Maintaining the various databases identify skill set shortages for short-term training requirements.
- Maintaining positive relationships with internal Customers and outsourced Vendors to ensure that joint goals are met
- Ad hoc tasks to support the business

REFERRENCES

Singtel: Mr.Sriram (Manager) 60102141258

Grab: Ms.Abby (Team Lead) 601131275680

Maxis: Ms.Emily Lopez (Manager) 60122950292

Customer Care Officer (GRAB)

September 2017 to July 2018

SALARYRM3500)

DIGITAL

• Identify target audience and grow our email list Design and implement direct email marketing campaigns Proofread emails for clarity, grammar and spelling Ensure mobile- friendly email templates Upgrade our email templates using personalization and advanced features Ensure prompt and accurate communication with clients via email to minimize unsubscribes Analyse campaign performance and suggest improvements Ensure emails follow industry policies and best practices.

SOCIALMEDIA

• Specifically responsible for developing and implementing social media plans and specific tactics across all channels of social media (Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, and more) for key annual events as well as additional opportunities as identified. Monitor and track all social 2 media initiatives and tactics implemented by organization and develop reports on those findings.

Customer Care Officer

SINGTEL

March 2015 to July 2017

SALARYRM2600)

• Answered an average of 20-30 calls per day by addressing customer inquiries (general inquiries, billing inquiries), solving problems (technical related) and providing new product information. Answered product questions with up-to-date knowledge of sales and store promotions. Investigated and resolved customer inquiries and complaints in a timely and empathetic manner. Ensured superior customer experience by addressing customer concerns, demonstrating empathy and resolving problems on the spot. Directed calls to appropriate individuals and departments.

Education

OPEN UNIVERSITY MALAYSIA

Present

Skills

PROBLEM SOLVER (Less than 1 year), TIME MANAGEMENT (Less than 1 year)

Additional Information

SKILLS

- Quick learner
- Creative problem solver
- Communication skills
- Ability to work under pressure
- Time management